{"componentChunkName":"component---src-templates-establishment-page-js","path":"/establishment/2285","result":{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2285","name":"Little Caesar's Pizza","address":"7633 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210","owner":"Sanrita Jones","licenseNumber":"042601","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"335","coords":"-83.13696,42.33078","geojson":{"id":"2285","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.136962533,42.330776868]},"properties":{"name":"Little Caesar's Pizza","owner":"Sanrita Jones","address":"7633 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":null,"license_number":"042601","establishmentid":"2285","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"335","most_recent_license_date":"2022-05-23"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"758","name":"Alaskan Bar Homestead #3","address":"7625 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"1009","name":"General George Patton Post #11","address":"4930 Central","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"5348","name":"Hard Bodies Bar","address":"7443  Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"760","name":"Hard Bodies","address":"7443 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"3612","name":"Tacos El Cunado #2","address":"4632 52nd","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"51623918","name":"Zizo's Pizza & Subs","address":"7801 Michigan Ave","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"1283","name":"Papa's Pizza & Subs","address":"7801 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"1132","name":"Cas Bar","address":"7800 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"3198","name":"Angel's Place","address":"7824 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"},{"establishmentid":"743","name":"Freer Bar","address":"7355 Michigan Ave.","zipcode":"48210"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"60426","inspectionDate":"2022-08-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"SIDE DOOR","subLocation":"PESTS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Cardboard","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Constructed from materials that are not","subProblem":"Durable, corrosion-resistant, and non-absorbent","location":"SHELF","subLocation":"Cardboard","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable materials."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"floor covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Ceiling vent cover(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"Door(s) of walk-in cooler","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"violationCode":"6-202.15","violationDescription":"Outer openings of a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT shall be protected against the entry of insects and rodents. Unless otherwise allowed by law. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Outer opening(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to prevent pest entry","subProblem":"","location":"SIDE DOOR","subLocation":"Openings","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"}]},{"inspectionid":"55399","inspectionDate":"2021-07-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"gnats","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"SIDE DOOR","subLocation":"PESTS","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Cardboard","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Constructed from materials that are not","subProblem":"Durable, corrosion-resistant, and non-absorbent","location":"SHELF","subLocation":"Cardboard","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable materials."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"floor covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Ceiling vent cover(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean"}]},{"inspectionid":"51900","inspectionDate":"2020-06-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"7-208.11","violationDescription":"First aid supplies that are in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT for the EMPLOYEES' use shall be:\n(A) Labeled as specified under § 7-101.11; (Pf) and   \n(B) Stored in a kit or a container that is located to prevent the contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"First aid supplies","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/with","subProblem":"Single-service/use items","location":"STORAGE AREA (DRY)","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-06-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate separation to prevent contamination."},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"at restroom handsink","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Handwashing soap","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-06-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2020-07-01T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"2-402.11","violationDescription":"FOOD EMPLOYEES shall wear hair restraints such as hats, hair coverings or nets, beard restraints, and clothing that covers body hair, that are designed and worn to effectively keep their hair from contacting exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; or unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE or SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Hair restraint","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not worn on head/hair","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"Hair Restraints/Covering","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide hat or hair net."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Floor drain(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Cardboard","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Constructed from materials that are not","subProblem":"Durable, corrosion-resistant, and non-absorbent","location":"SHELF","subLocation":"Cardboard","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable materials."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"floor covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."}]},{"inspectionid":"51899","inspectionDate":"2020-06-23T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"48392","inspectionDate":"2019-07-16T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Floor drain(s)","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.11","violationDescription":"(A) A HANDWASHING SINK shall be maintained so that it is accessible at all times for EMPLOYEE use and used for no other purpose. (Pf)\n(B)  An automatic handwashing facility shall be used in accordance with manufacturer's instructions. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily accessible","subProblem":"Items stored In front of","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Handsink","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-08-06T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-101.19","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT that are exposed to splash, spillage, or other FOOD soiling or that require frequent cleaning shall be constructed of a CORROSION-RESISTANT, nonabsorbent, and SMOOTH material.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Cardboard","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Constructed from materials that are not","subProblem":"Durable, corrosion-resistant, and non-absorbent","location":"SHELF","subLocation":"Cardboard","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide smooth, durable, non-absorbent, easily cleanable materials."},{"violationCode":"6-202.14","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a toilet room located on the PREMISES shall be completely enclosed and provided with a tight-fitting and self-closing door. \n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Toilet room(s)","subItem":"employee","problemDescription":"Not provided with","subProblem":"Self-closing door","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Door","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide self-closing door."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Facility","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-08-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Clean"},{"violationCode":"3-501.11","violationDescription":"Stored frozen FOODS shall be maintained frozen.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Frozen food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not frozen solid","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"Frozen Food(s)","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain frozen."},{"violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"floor covering(s)","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Easily cleanable","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Floor tiles","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"violationCode":"6-501.14","violationDescription":"(A) Intake and exhaust air ducts shall be cleaned and filters changed so they are not a source of contamination by dust, dirt, and other materials. \n(B) If vented to the outside, ventilation systems may not create a public health HAZARD or nuisance or unLAWful discharge.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Ventilation system","subItem":"intake air ducts","problemDescription":"Not clean","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Vent cover","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"42690","inspectionDate":"2018-06-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"in ladies restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"BATHROOM","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"False","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"39613","inspectionDate":"2017-08-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38813","inspectionDate":"2017-05-21T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.18","violationDescription":"A FOOD specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A) or (B) shall be discarded if it:  \n    (1) Exceeds the temperature and time combination specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A),              except time that the product is frozen; (P)\n    (2) Is in a container or PACKAGE that does not bear a date or day; (P) or\n    (3) Is appropriately marked with a date or day that exceeds a temperature and              time combination as specified in ¶ 3-501.17(A). (P)  \n\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"Refrigerator","subLocation":"","corrected":"True","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2017-05-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"37773","inspectionDate":"2017-01-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"37909","inspectionDate":"2017-01-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2023-04-25T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2285"}},"staticQueryHashes":["3649515864","63159454"]}